sexforums.com 2013-04-04

# SexForums Privacy Policy

**SexForums.com Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy (the " _Policy_ ") applies to all websites operated by SexForums.com and its affiliates (the " _Website_ "  " _Websites_ " or " _Our Websites_ ").  SexForums.com ("SexForums", " _us_ " or " _we_ ") understands that the privacy of its members, subscribers, guests and/or visitors (" _Members_ ", " _you_ " or " _your_ ") is very important. We've developed this Policy to ensure that your privacy is protected while using any of Our Websites.

** 1\. This Website Is For Adults Only**

Children under eighteen years of age are prohibited from using Our Websites or any of our services. We ask that children never submit information to us.  All members and persons appearing on this site have represented to us that they are 18 years of age or older.

** 2\. Information We Collect**

During the registration process for any of the Websites, you may provide us with certain Personal Information  (" _PI_ ") including, but not limited to, your name, address, email address, and IP address.

Our Websites also use "cookies" to store and sometimes track information to make your online experience easier and more personalized. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies may record information a user accesses on one webpage to simplify subsequent interactions with that website by the same user, or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related webpages. Cookies make it easier for a user to move from webpage to webpage and to complete transactions over the Internet.

Most major web browsers are set up so that they will initially accept cookies, but you may modify your computer's preferences to issue you an alert when a cookie is downloaded, or to disable the ability of third parties to download a cookie to you. If you choose to reject all cookies, there are areas of our Websites that may not function properly. You may obtain further information about cookies and how they function at:  [ http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).

We may also use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons or 1x1 "gifs" and other similar technologies (collectively "Pixel Tags"), to track your use of Our Websites. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel (1x1), that is ordinarily not visible to Site visitors and may be associated with cookies on the visitors' hard drives. We also may include Pixel Tags in advertisements or promotional or other e-mail messages, or to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information enables us to customize the services we offer. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other Website users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on our Website, we may collect such information into a file that is accessed only by authorized SexForums personnel or representatives. We may also collect other Members' comments about you.

** 3\. Our Use of Your Personal Information ** 

We use your PI internally to analyze Website usage, improve our content and product offerings, allow personalized content, help categorize members, improve our marketing efforts, and customize Our Websites' content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve Our Websites and better tailor your online experience.

We may also use your PI to deliver information that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as categorizing members or content who have similar interests or are from similar geographies, or personalize banners and promotions.

We also send you periodic informational updates via email.

We may use PI to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce any agreements, policies and rules governing the use of our Websites.

We DO NOT sell or rent any of your PI to third parties for marketing purposes without your permission. We do, however, provide your PI to our service providers as reasonably necessary or appropriate to provide services on the Websites.

We do disclose anonymous information in the aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose information in any form that could be used to identify you personally such as your Website password.

In response to compulsory (required) governmental and/or third party inquiries, we may disclose PI to comply with a court order, subpoena, and search warrant. We expressly reserve the right to disclose your PI when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, or to enforce our agreements, policies, and rules governing your use of the Website, or to cooperate voluntarily with law enforcement inquiries.

We may share or transfer some or all of your PI among our family of companies, or to one or more non- family entities that acquire some or all of the business in which that PI is used or maintained.

** 4\. Your Use of Websites' Members' Information**

You may not use another Websites' Members' information, whether private or not, for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. We reserve the right to terminate those who misuse other Members' information or who otherwise violate any user agreements, policies, or rules governing the use of our Website.

** 5\. Do Not Disclose Your PI or Password**

Please DO NOT post, share or disclose in public forums, e.g., chat rooms, blogs, any PI that you do not wish other Members to know. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your PI to others. Similarly, you should never disclose or share your password with anyone else. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your PI and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password and/or contact us at  [ privacy@sexforums.com](mailto:privacy@sexforums.com).

** 6\. Reviewing, Changing or Removing Your Personal Information **  

Once you register, you will be able to review and change much of your PI including, but not limited to:

  * Your email address
  * Your city, state, ZIP or other postal code, country
  * Your password
  * Your profile

Please promptly update your information by logging in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge you to change your password periodically to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your account information.

** 7\. Third Party Collections of Information; Ad Tracking**

This Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your PI to others while using Our Websites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to its use, maintenance, or disclosure.  We do not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable.

We may use third party companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies or Pixel Tags to measure advertising effectiveness.

** 8\. Security**

 Websites use reasonable security measures to help protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use industry standard efforts, such as firewalls, to safeguard your PI information. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, or elsewhere, our technical staff works hard to help ensure your secure use of our services.

** 9\. Update/Delete/Opt-Out**

You have the following choices to modify or delete your PI from our database:

* Send an email to  [ privacy@sexforums.com](mailto:privacy@sexforums.com)  
* Log in with your password and modify/delete your profile  
* Submit a form through the contact us page

By using the above contact information, you may also receive emails from third party advertisers.

** 10\. Revisions to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, in our sole and absolute discretion, to revise, amend, modify or revoke this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner to the fullest extent permitted by law. Changes to this Policy will be effective by posting revisions on the Website.
